//creating an array and passing the number, question, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question:"In which year Cristiano Ronaldo setr the record for of 11 goals in a single group stage?",
        answer: "2015/16",
        options:[
            "2010/11",
            "2012/13",
            "2016/17",
            "2015/16"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question:"Which African player had the most Champions league apperances?",
        answer: "Didier Drogba",
        options:[
            "Samuel Eto'o",
            "Didier Drogba",
            "koko Toure",
            "Michael Essien"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question:"Who is the all time Champions league top scorer?",
        answer: "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        options:[
            "Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "Lionel Messi",
            "Sergio Aguero",
            "Harry Maguire"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question:"Who scored the fastest goal in the Champions league history?",
        answer: "Roy Makaay",
        options:[
            "Roy Makaay",
            "Paolo Maldini",
            "Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "Samuel Eto'o"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question:"Which club has won the most no of Champions league?",
        answer: "Real Madrid",
        options:[
            "Liverpool",
            "Real Madrid",
            "Manchester United",
            "Barcelona"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question:"Which player has made the most Champions league appearances?",
        answer: "Iker Casillas",
        options:[
            "Xavi",
            "Iker Casillas",
            "Sergio Ramos",
            "Gianluigi Buffon"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question:"Who is the only defender to score a Champions League Hatt-rick?",
        answer: "Layvin Kurzawa",
        options:[
            "Roberto Carlos",
            "Layvin kurzawa",
            "Cesc Fabregas",
            "Eric Di Meco"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question:"Who has written the Champions league Anthem?",
        answer: "tony Britten",
        options:[
            "Ludovico Einaudi",
            "Tony Britten",
            "Lothar Matthaus",
            "Ennio Morricone"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question:"How many teams compete at the group stage of the Champions League?",
        answer: "32",
        options:[
            "48",
            "40",
            "28",
            "32"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question:"Which club holds the record for the most Champions League defeat?",
        answer: "FC Porto",
        options:[
            "Real Madrid",
            "Juventus",
            "FC Porto",
            "Liverpool"
        ]
    },
];